Now, let's go to the console and take a quick look.
So I'm on AWS console.
So let me just search for Compray.
So here is Amazon Compray.
So now I'm on the homepage of Amazon Compray.
And you can see here Amazon Compray and Natural Language,
Processing, and Text Analysis.
So if I just click on Launch, and you can see
there are two types here.
One is the real-time analysis.
And another is the analysis of the job.
And it's very similar to what we had seen earlier
with translate.
So you can create the job name, and then do the analysis type,
whether you want to do entity recognition, key phrases,
PI identification, sentiment analysis, and so on.
You can provide the job name, let me just say demo.
And then you can choose whether you want to do entity recognition,
key phrases, identifying the PI data, sentiment analysis,
and so on.
So let me just click on PI.
And then you have to choose the language.
So maybe it supports two right now.
I think English and Spanish, so you can choose English.
So here, you can see in the output mode,
it can either do an offset.
The job output provides character offset
that locate each PI entity in the input text.
So it can identify the PI entity, or it can do reduction.
So you provide the input data here.
So you applaud the document in an S3 location
and provide that S3 location here.
You suggest what is the file format.
And then you suggest the location of the output data.
Again, it's the S3 bucket.
So you create an S3 bucket and provide the location
for output data.
So that's the scenario where you want to do the batch analysis.
But you can also do real time analysis.
So if I just go here and if I do built in--
so this is some sample data, they have provided here--
you can also do a custom and provide your own input.
So let me just build, do, built in.
And let me ask it to analyze this data
that they have already provided.
So now below, you can see the results.
So based on this input data, you can see it
has created various entities.
It has analyzed this text, and it's showing here.
So it's the name of the person.
And again, John is the name of person, organization,
name of the organization, phone number,
and some other things that it has identified from here.
So if I go to key phrases, then it's identifying the key phrases.
So here, it's identifying the key phrases.
Then language, you can see it's saying that 0.99 confidence
that it's English, then if I look at the PI data,
so you can either do offset or do a label.
And here, it's showing that the PI data that they have
is name, email, bank, account number, and so on.
Then it does sentiment analysis.
So you can see it's given some score for sentiment.
So neutral is 0.14, positive is 0.13, negative 0,
and mixed is 0.7.
And then you have targeted sentiment.
So what is the sentiment for the person, the organization,
and it seems mostly all is neutral.
And then finally, you have the syntax.
OK, that's pretty much it from this lecture.
So hopefully, you have got a high level understanding
of how Amazon Comprehend works.
I'll see you in the next lecture.
Thank you.